problem-attic.com 2018-07-23

# Problem-Attic

Problem-Attic is a web-based program developed by EducAide Software. We are pleased to make the program available to everyone in the educational community: teachers, academic coaches, tutors, homeschoolers, researchers, etc. 

Because of the wide appeal of Problem-Attic and its many possible uses (classroom instruction, assessment, blended and self-paced learning), you should carefully read this Privacy Policy and related Terms of Service to see what rules govern your particular situation. If you do not accept the rules, then you should not make any further use of Problem-Attic. 

### 1\. Collection of Information

EducAide Software (“EAS”) collects and stores certain types of personal information, as follows: 

  * In order to make use of Problem-Attic (the “Program”), you must create an account. If you choose to do so, then EAS will ask for your first and last name and your email address. As an option, you may provide EAS with the name of your school and/or a job description. EAS requires you to confirm your email address for your account to be activated. 

  * After creating an account, you may use the features of the Program that are freely-available without providing EAS any additional personal information. You may, however, provide other information voluntarily through the Settings options in the Program, or through separate communications with EAS, such as a request for technical support. 

  * If you create an account, then EAS will collect information about your documents. This includes, among other things, the questions you have chosen, your formatting options, and whether you created/downloaded a PDF version of the document or exported the questions to another program. 

  * Regardless of whether you create an account, EAS will collect information about your general use of the Program, such as the pages that you visit and whether you have taken the Problem-Attic Tour. EAS will also collect details that are publicly-available about your web browser and computer, such as IP address and operating system. 

  * If you become part of a school-wide subscription, then EAS will know the name of your employer and possibly the grades and subjects that you teach. Also, certain information about your use, such as number of documents and last log-in, will become known to the person(s) in charge of the subscription at your school. 

### 2\. Safeguarding and Use of Information

EAS stores the information it collects securely on its own or other host servers. (EAS uses some third-party vendors to provide hardware, software, networking, storage, and related technologies required to run the Program.) 

EAS may use the information it collects to improve Program performance and quality of service, to study operation of the Program and user preferences, and to notify you of changes to the Program, including service interruptions, bugfixes, new features, or changes to Terms of Service or this Privacy Policy. 

Except for the following two provisions, the information collected by EAS will _not_ be sold, traded, bartered, given away, or used for solication by a third-party without your explicit permission. 

EAS may share the information it collects with an agent or direct affiliate, such as a content- or application-development partner or a company hired by EAS to assist with emails, newsletters, marketing, and other customer and public relations activities. 

EAS may share the information it collects with third-parties, as EAS deems necessary, to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving threats to another person, violations of Terms of Service, or as otherwise required by law. 

### 3\. Cookies

A cookie is a small amount of data, often including an anonymous unique identifier, which a web server sends to your browser and which gets saved on your local hard drive. In order to use the Program, you may need to change your browser settings so that it can save cookies. 

EAS uses cookies to record your current session information and, at your option, to store login information. 

EAS does _not_ put any cookies on your computer that track your other web-browsing activities, that track websites you visit after using the Program, or that make any attempt to uncover any additional personal information about you. 

EAS makes use of third-party tools like Google Analytics for the purpose of monitoring website traffic and improving performance. These third-party tools may put their own cookies on your computer. EAS does _not_ use them to collect information about you, nor do we provide the third parties with your account details. They may, however, be able to associate your IP address and email through data which they collect independently. 

### 4\. Student Privacy

EAS designed Problem-Attic to be a teacher tool that is used only indirectly by students. Here _indirect_ means that a teacher creates a document and then provides it to students. EAS cannot know, however, whether a user of the Program is actually a teacher. It is possible for a student to sign up for an account and then create documents for his/her own use. In that case, the student would be subject to this Privacy Policy. 

The Program has scoring options that students may interact with through a teacher’s account. (These options are available to subscribing schools and for free trial in what is called the Play Area.) If a teacher makes use of the scoring options, then EAS will collect limited information from students and will use it only to create reports for the teacher. _EAS never stores personally identifiable information about students._

Here are further details about the scoring options and the safeguarding of student information: 

  * The Program does not use class rosters. At the teacher’s option, students can submit their answers with first name only, initials, or any other identifier. 

  * The Program does not authenticate students. For that reason, the results are meaningful only to the teacher. To anyone else, the results are essentially _anonymized_. 

  * The Program does not keep individual student records. All data which is collected is _ad hoc_. It is for a single test or quiz, and teachers can delete it at any time. 

  * The Program can be used for self-guided learning. In this case, no information is collected and stored, and the purpose of scoring is to show students their own results. 

  * The Program does _not_ use cookies for online tests or other student-facing pages, and it makes no attempt to identify or track website use by students who visit those pages. 

  * The Program stores all information using industry best practices for security and encryption. 

### 5\. Changes

EAS reserves the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. If we make any significant changes, we will notify you by email (using the address you supplied when you created an account), and we will announce the changes on the Problem-Attic website and on your document home page, which you see after creating an account and logging in. It then becomes your responsibility to review the changes and decide if you agree with them. If you do not, then you should discontinue use of the Program. 

### 6\. Contact Information

If you have questions or would like to comment on this Privacy Policy, please contact us by phone or email. 

**EducAide Software**   
PO Box 1048   
Vallejo, CA 94590 USA   
800-669-9405 toll-free   
707-554-6505 local   
707-554-9600 fax   
Email: [support@problem-attic.com](mailto:support@problem-attic.com)
